Hi everyone, my name is Joshua,
大家好，我叫 Joshua，
co-founder of Overseez, and today I'm going to quickly show you how to use
是 Overseez 的联合创始人。今天我将快速向大家展示如何使用
our website. So first, on the homepage,
我们的网站。首先，在首页上，
you're going to see this button, Try AI Now,
你会看到这个“Try AI Now”按钮，
you're going to press that. The search bar here,
点击它。这里的搜索栏，
where you can look at anything you want, whether it's products,
你可以搜索任何你想找的内容，无论是产品、
services, or places, you can also change your location and currency
服务还是地点，你也可以随时更改你的位置和货币，
at any time, so everything is personalized to where you are.
这样所有内容都会根据你所在地进行个性化。
So right here, if you click this button, Refresh, you'll change your location,
就在这里，如果你点击这个“Refresh”按钮，就可以更改位置，
and right here, you can change your currency. So right now,
在这里，你可以更改货币。现在，
I'm going to change to Canadian dollars because I'm located in Canada,
我要换成加元，因为我位于加拿大，
and you can search anything you want. Let's try apple juice.
你可以搜索任何你想要的东西。让我们试一下苹果汁。
I want to buy apple juice,
我想买苹果汁，
and one of our best features is that you can enter your bank name
我们最棒的功能之一是你可以输入你的银行名称，
to instantly see the fees you would pay abroad. So I'm going to enter my bank
立即查看你在国外需要支付的费用。现在我要输入我的银行
name, and I'm going to type in my details
名称，并输入我的详细信息，
and see how much I can save
立即查看每次购买
on each purchase right away. So right here we can see our five options.
可以节省多少钱。在这里我们可以看到五个选项。
You can see the price, you can see the overseas fee you would pay
你可以看到价格，可以看到使用银行卡需要支付的
with your card, the average price of the area of the product,
海外手续费、该地区该产品的平均价格，
and how much you're saving. So right here the average of an apple
以及你节省了多少。在这里，苹果汁的
juice is three dollars twenty five,
平均价格是 3.25 美元，
but with our AI you found a discount and it only cost
但通过我们的 AI，你找到了折扣，它只需要
one dollar twenty seven, so you'd be saving one dollar ninety four.
1.27 美元，这样你就节省了 1.94 美元。
So how does it work? You just go here. You like this.
那么它是如何运作的呢？你只需要点这里。如果你喜欢这个
This option Walmart, you click here.
Walmart 选项，点击这里。
I saved here and you click log saving.
“I saved here”，然后点击“Log saving”。
So as you can see, it's already saved.
如你所见，它已经保存好了。
And here at this bottom view on maps, if you like something,
而在底部的“View on maps”，如果你看中某个地方，
you just click the button and it'll take you directly to Google Maps.
只需点击按钮，它就会直接带你进入 Google Maps。
So you can easily get there. And now we go to our
这样你就能轻松到达那里。现在我们去
dashboard and you'll see a progress bar that tracks how much money you've saved
控制面板，你会看到一个进度条，追踪你通过使用
using our AI and our discounts.
我们的 AI 和折扣节省了多少钱。
And right here in recent savings, you can also keep track of everything you've
在“Recent savings”中，你也可以追踪你节省的
been saving, including the place right here,
每一笔开支，包括地点、
the date and the exact amount all in one spot.
日期和具体金额，全都集中在一处。
So that's it. It's really simple, fast and built to help you save smarter
就是这样。操作非常简单、快速，旨在帮助你通过 Overseez
with Overseez. Thank you guys.
更聪明地省钱。谢谢大家。